import { createStore } from 'vuex'
export default createStore({
    state: { 
        players: {
            player1name: "",
            player2name: "",
            winner: null, 
            unused: true
        },
        currentQuestion: null,
        firstQuestions: [
            {
                id: 1000,
                question: "",
                hint: "",
                answer: "",
                winner: null, 
                
            },
            {
                id: 1001,
                question: "Which CSS property can IKEA use for table sales marketing?",
                hint: "DT",
                answer: "display: table",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1002,
                question: "What does SASS stand for?",
                hint: "SCSS",
                answer: "Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1003,
                question: "What does BEM stand for?",
                hint: "BEM",
                answer: "Block Element Modificator",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1004,
                question: "What is the current version of HTML",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "5",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1005,
                question: "What does HTML stand for?",
                hint: "HTML",
                answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
                winner: null,
            },
            {
                id: 1006,
                question: "What is the most popuplar and really old website about web development in ČR ?",
                hint: "JWB",
                answer: "jakpsatweb.cz",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1007,
                question: "What HTML attribute do I use to open a link in a new tab?",
                hint: "TB",
                answer: "target='_blank'",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1008,
                question: "How do I round a number up using javascript?",
                hint: "MR",
                answer: "Math.round()",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1009,
                question: "What event do I capture the loss of focus from the input in javascript?",
                hint: "O",
                answer: "onfocusout/focusout",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10010,
                question: "What character is short for jQuery?",
                hint: "D",
                answer: "$",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10011,
                question: "What is the answer to the question of life, the universe and everything?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "42",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10012,
                question: "What's the name of a character from the IT Crowds series with a funny hairstyle?",
                hint: "MM",
                answer: "Maurice Moss",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10013,
                question: "What is the name of the image that appears in the browser tab next to the page title?",
                hint: "F",
                answer: "favicon",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10014,
                question: "What command does create a new git repository?",
                hint: "G",
                answer: "git init",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10015,
                question: "What is the name of a programming language that consists of only 8 commands",
                hint: "B",
                answer: "Brainfuck",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10016,
                question: "What code does the Internal Server Error have in the HTTP header?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "500",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10017,
                question: "What code does Unathorized have in the HTTP header?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "401",
                winner: null,
            },
            {
                id: 10018,
                question: "What's the emergency number in the IT Crowd?",
                hint: "0118 ...",
                answer: "0118 999 881 999 119 725 3",
                winner: null,
            },
            {
                id: 10019,
                question: "What does number 43 mean in the Big Bang series?",
                hint: "SR",
                answer: "Sheldons record in hackisack",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10020,
                question: "What does UTFG stand for?",
                hint: "UTFG",
                answer: "Use the fucking google",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 10021,
                question: "What does WWW stand for?",
                hint: "WWW",
                answer: "world wide web",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1022,
                question: "Which one is the first web browser invented in 1990",
                hint: "N",
                answer: "Nexus",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1023,
                question: "Number of bits used by the IPv6 address",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "128 bit",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1024,
                question: "Which one programming language is exclusively used for artificial intelligence",
                hint: "P",
                answer: "Prolog",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1025,
                question: "Which programming language is used to create programs like applets?",
                hint: "J",
                answer: "Java",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1026,
                question: "First computer virus is known as",
                hint: "CV",
                answer: "Creeper Virus",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1027,
                question: "Who programmed the first computer game 'Spacewar!' in 1962",
                hint: "SR",
                answer: "Steave Russell",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1028,
                question: "Who created the C programming Language",
                hint: "DR",
                answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1029,
                question: "Who is known as the father of internet",
                hint: "VC",
                answer: "Vint Cerf",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1030,
                question: "Which operating system is developed and used by Apple Inc",
                hint: "i",
                answer: "iOS",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1031,
                question: "Computer Hard Disk was first introduced in 1956 by",
                hint: "I",
                answer: "IBM",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1032,
                question: "What is a default 'text editor' for Microsoft Windows?",
                hint: "N",
                answer: "Notepad",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1033,
                question: "Which key combination is used to minimize all open windows and displays in the screen",
                hint: "Win+?",
                answer: "Win+D",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1034,
                question: "Which key combination is used to close a open application in Windows machine",
                hint: "?+?",
                answer: "Alt+F4",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1035,
                question: "Which function key needs to be press during reboot to enter in Safe Mode of a Windows machine",
                hint: "F?",
                answer: "F8",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1036,
                question: "Which key combination is used to permanently delete a file or folder",
                hint: "?+del",
                answer: "Shift+del",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1037,
                question: "Which web browser is developed by the Google",
                hint: "C",
                answer: "Chrome",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1038,
                question: "Mark Zuckerberg is the owner of",
                hint: "M",
                answer: "Meta (old Facebook)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1039,
                question: "What is the full form of PDF",
                hint: "PDF",
                answer: "Portable document format",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1040,
                question: "Text connected to page is",
                hint: "HL",
                answer: "Hyperlink",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1041,
                question: "Saving a file from the Internet onto your desktop is called",
                hint: "D",
                answer: "Downloading",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1042,
                question: "Errors in computer programmes are called",
                hint: "Bugs",
                answer: "Bugs",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1043,
                question: "The exact meaning of the term VPN is?",
                hint: "VPN",
                answer: "Virtual Private Network",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1044,
                question: "What does the shortcut BSOD stands for?",
                hint: "BSOD",
                answer: "Blue screen of death",
                winner: null, 
            },

            // From Peter QA
            {
                id: 1045,
                question: "What is a pre-requisite if you want to fix 'jedinou picovinku'?",
                hint: "R C T",
                answer: "Rozdelat cely traktor",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1046,
                question: "Who is the author of fan's favorite Czech website http://milujipraci.cz/.",
                hint: "A",
                answer: "Arguit - Frantisek Zahora",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1047,
                question: "Who is presumably the only person from Chyron Brno office who has an existing wikipedia page about himself/herself.",
                hint: "MK",
                answer: "Marie Kurkova",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1048,
                question: "How long was the code freeze period before Axis release 2.0 (tolerance - 1hr).",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "0",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1049,
                question: "How many unique official US releases (at least half of the modules deployed) Axis team had in the last 12 months?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "4 (1.0, 2.0, 2.1.0, 2.2.0)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1050,
                question: "Name all 3 main brands (divisions) of Chyronhego?",
                hint: "CTH",
                answer: "Chyron Tracab Hego",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1051,
                question: "In which year was the Chyron Corporation (later Chyronhego Corporation) established?",
                hint: "19xx",
                answer: "1966",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1052,
                question: "Name all the members of Axis front-end team and sort them by seniority (start with the most junior one)",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Maroš Janota",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1053,
                question: "Name the last 3 people who had a role of product manager of Axis in Chyronhego.",
                hint: "KK, JM, PM",
                answer: "Knut Karlsen, Jim Martinolich, Peter Matis",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1054,
                question: "Name at least 3 job positions which Patrik Svikruha had (or still has) in Chyronhego.",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Tech led, Architect, Devops engineer, Product owner, Teamleader, HR agency - basically any answer is correct",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1055,
                question: "Name the 6 end user facing modules of Axis (Portal excluded, start with your personal favorite).",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Charts, Maps, News, Order, Quotes, Track",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1056,
                question: "How many people were part of the HR department of Chyronhego in summer 2020.",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "0",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1057,
                question: "What is the estimated time which Pavel needs, in order to completely rework the entire maps module?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "One weekend",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1058,
                question: "What is the most favorite work assignment of Frantisek Zahora? (His point of view on the correct answer may be slightly different).",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "DB",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1059,
                question: "Who is at the moment the oldest team member of Axis Brno team?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Celyn",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1060,
                question: "How many kids (combined) the Axis (CZE) team members have? Official ones only, we don't count with 'What happened in Vegas - stays in Vegas' kind of kids.",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "6",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1061,
                question: "What was the estimated duration of 'Axis migration to cloud' by the former CTO of Chyronhego? (tolerance one day).",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "One day",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1062,
                question: "How many people with a name Ilona are currently employed in Chyronhego?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "2",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1063,
                question: "What is the country of origin of Chyronhego's CEO - Ariel Garcia?",
                hint: "A",
                answer: "Argentina",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1064,
                question: "Which sport equipment is Yomi using as a part of his morning routine?",
                hint: "T",
                answer: "Treadmill",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1065,
                question: "What is Mathieu's hobby?",
                hint: "C",
                answer: "Cars",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1066,
                question: "What is a typical Christmas gift in Chyronhego Czech?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Bottle of gin",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1067,
                question: "What is Mathieu's job title listed in his profile on slack?",
                hint: "COS",
                answer: "Chief of stuff",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1068,
                question: "What is AG's job title listed in his profile on slack?",
                hint: "CEO",
                answer: "Chief Escalation Officer",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1069,
                question: "What is Mike Truex's job title listed in his profile on slack?",
                hint: "CFO",
                answer: "Chief Fun Officer",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1070,
                question: "What was Patrik's job title listed in his profile on slack while he was a product owner?",
                hint: "ACC",
                answer: "Axis call center",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1071,
                question: "What is Peter's job title listed in his profile on slack?",
                hint: "PM",
                answer: "Pro duck manager",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1072,
                question: "What is the name of Frantisek's band?",
                hint: "E",
                answer: "Edain",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1073,
                question: "Which PC game is played the most by Axis team members (commonly)?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Battlefield V",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1074,
                question: "Which team/pair dominated the desktop game Activity during the Axis teambuilding?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Maros & Katka",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1075,
                question: "What was the cottage name where the first official Axis (CZE) teambuilding was conducted?",
                hint: "ChUF",
                answer: "Chalupa u Frysavky",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1076,
                question: "How many Slovaks are part of the Axis team (incl. Axis contributors)",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "5 (Katka, Maros, Patrik, Peter, Samuel)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1077,
                question: "Name the 2 brands of beer which were the main beverage on Axis (CZE) teambuilding:",
                hint: "🍻",
                answer: "Kozel, Nachmelena Opice",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1078,
                question: "How many animation options are available in Axis Charts for a chart type: pie?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "3",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1079,
                question: "What is the name of both of the third party image banks in Axis?",
                hint: "A&G",
                answer: "AP, Getty Images",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1080,
                question: "What is the Jira work item number of the famous Axis Maps issue",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "2047",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1081,
                question: "Which mythological creature has Axis “tattooed” on its forehead?",
                hint: "U",
                answer: "Unicorn",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1082,
                question: "How many cars were used to transport 10 people (from Chyronhego) to the cottage where Axis (CZE) teambuilding took place? ",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "6",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1083,
                question: "Which animal is always there to assist you with any questions you may have during your development / testing activities on Axis?",
                hint: "D",
                answer: "Rubber duck (Patrik’s gift)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1084,
                question: "What is the first animal printed on the 3D printer owned by Maros?",
                hint: "A",
                answer: "Ant",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1085,
                question: "What are the first names of 2 past Axis developers M. Gioino and E. Harokopakis (no typo here)?",
                hint: "M&E",
                answer: "Michael & Emmanuel",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1086,
                question: "Which company is a majority shareholder of Chyronhego?",
                hint: "AGM",
                answer: "Apollo Global Management",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1087,
                question: "Who are the 4 people on the main screen of the Axis Matrix theme?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Ilona, Patrik, Pavel, Peter",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1088,
                question: "Which musical instrument is Jiri playing on?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Guitar",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1100,
                question: "How many repositories are there in axis? (+- 2)",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "17 or 16",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1102,
                question: "How many product managers are in Brno?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "One",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1103,
                question: "Who has the most comments on pull requests?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Patrik",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1104,
                question: "Who is the NO.1 reviewer of pull requests?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Pavel",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1105,
                question: "How many members have Axis team? (Including contributors)",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "13 (10 - members in Brno, 3 contributors)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1107,
                question: "What does the shortcut LINQ stands for?",
                hint: "LINQ",
                answer: "Language Integrated Query",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1109,
                question: "Which text format do we use for documentation?",
                hint: "M",
                answer: "Markdown",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1110,
                question: "In which language are written our deployment scripts?",
                hint: "R",
                answer: "Ruby",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1112,
                question: "How is called a dynamic documentation for our Specflow tests that are generated from `axis/test` project?",
                hint: "LD",
                answer: "LivingDoc",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1113,
                question: "How is called package manager that we are using in .NET?",
                hint: "N",
                answer: "Nuget",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1114,
                question: "Which test framework/runner we are using in our axis/tests project?",
                hint: "XU",
                answer: "xUnit - We are also migrating all tests to this",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1115,
                question: "What is the name of the new `News module` frontend?",
                hint: "C",
                answer: "Compose",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1116,
                question: "How many Software Enginners are required to approve pull request to `master` branch?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "2",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1117,
                question: "How long is Patrik's ponny tail? (+- 5cm)",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "40 cm",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1118,
                question: "Who saved us from thirst on Axis (CZE) teambuilding?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "Katka",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1119,
                question: "How many smokers (cigarettes only) do we have in Axis Brno?",
                hint: "INT",
                answer: "2 (Pavel & Katka)",
                winner: null, 
            },
            
            {
                id: 1120,
                question: "Which city is Katka’s hometown?",
                hint: "S",
                answer: "Senice",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1121,
                question: "Which brand of beer is tasting the worst but for some reason is Jiri’s favorite? (This question was downloaded from the internet and for sure was not created by Peter)",
                hint: "R",
                answer: "Radegast",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1122,
                question: "On which faculty is Samuel’s studying right now?",
                hint: "N/A",
                answer: "FIT",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 1123,
                question: "What is the name of Samuel’s favorite teacher? (Samuel’s point of view may be slightly different but WE DONT CARE)",
                hint: "PS",
                answer: "Patrik Svikruha",
                winner: null, 
            }
        ],
        secondQuestions: [
            {
                id: 2001,
                question: "Is Javascript case-sensitive ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "A",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2002,
                question: "Is Javascript the same as is Java ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2003,
                question: "Is C# the same as is C++ ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2004,
                question: "Could a semicolon be used in brainfuck?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2005,
                question: "Is it possible to create HelloWorld in javascript using only six characters? (not code length)",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y - JsFuck",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2006,
                question: "Has a Holly supercomputer from IQ 8000 ? (Which is like 8,000 gym teachers)",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - 6000",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2007,
                question: "Was google the first search engine in internet?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Archie",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2008,
                question: "Is Firewall in computer used for Authentication?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Security",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2009,
                question: "Is COBOL a database management software?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2010,
                question: "Is .gif an extension for videos?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2011,
                question: " Is WordStar the first word processor application?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2012,
                question: "Is RAM volatile memory in a computer system?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2013,
                question: "One Terabyte (1 TB) is equal to 1000GB",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - 1024GB",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2014,
                question: "Was Windows the first fully supported 64-bit operating system?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Linux",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2015,
                question: "Is MOSAIC a web browser ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            },
            {
                id: 2016,
                question: "Is Trojan a computer virus ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Malware",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2017,
                question: "Is SMTP Protocol used to receive an e-mail?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Pop3",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2018,
                question: "Is Pop3 Protocol used to receive an e-mail?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2019,
                question: "Was '@' sign first chosen for its use in e-mail address before 1975?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y - 1972",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2020,
                question: "Is monitor an Input device ?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - output",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2021,
                question: "Is Firefox used as an search engine?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - it's browser",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2022,
                question: "Are cookies stored on the server?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - on the client",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2023,
                question: "Antivirus protect systems from hackers",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Firewall",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2024,
                question: "USB Hard disk is a secondary type of storage device",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2025,
                question: "'IoT' refers to - Internet Organisation of Telecommunication",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Internet of Things",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2026,
                question: "Who is a shared resource for both Camio and Axis.",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y ",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2027,
                question: "Does Jim Martinolich own a boat?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2028,
                question: "Is the September 11 attack (2001) the reason why the development of the first ever version of Maps module got postponed?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2029,
                question: "Is Jirka a singer?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2030,
                question: "Is the number of created Jira work items created since Dec 14th 2020 in the Axis project higher than 1000?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2031,
                question: "Is Patrik proficient in martial arts?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2032,
                question: "Is Patrik’s dog named Kevin?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Merlin",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2033,
                question: "Are Maps the most used module in Axis by the entire customer group?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Order",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2034,
                question: "Are Quotes the least used module in Axis by the entire customer group?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Y",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2035,
                question: "Is .NET 5 direct successor of .NET 4.7.2?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "No, it is direct successor of .NET Core",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2036,
                question: "Is Transport Tycoon part of the Axis?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "No",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2037,
                question: "Do we have a monorepo?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Yes (Axis repository)",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2038,
                question: "Do we have some part of axis (incuding infrastructure) runing on Cloud?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Yes (Configuration harvestor)",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2039,
                question: "Is age difference between Martin's kids more than 13yo?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "Yes",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2040,
                question: "Was the brand of rum which Maros got when his youngest baby was born a Diplomatico?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Blue Mauritius",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
            {
                id: 2041,
                question: "Did Martin get a bottle of rum as a gift from Axis team members when his youngest kid was born?",
                hint: "Y/N",
                answer: "N - Bottle of Frndzlica",
                winner: null, 
            }, 
        ]
    },
    mutations: {
        SET_PLAYERS_NAMES(state, value) {
            state.players = value
        },
        SET_WINNER(state, value) {
            state.players.winner = value
        },
        SET_QUESTION(state, value) {
            state.currentQuestion = value
        }
    },
    actions: {
    },
    getters: {
        getFirstQeustionsList: state => {
            var qList = []
            var allQuestions = state.firstQuestions
            for (let q = 0; q < 21; q++) {
                var random = Math.floor(Math.random()*(allQuestions.length - 1)) + 1 
                qList.push(allQuestions[random])
                allQuestions.splice(random, 1)
            } 
            return qList
        },
        getSecondQeustionsList: state => {
            var qList = []
            var allQuestions = state.secondQuestions
            for (let q = 0; q < 21; q++) {
                var random = Math.floor(Math.random()*(allQuestions.length - 1)) + 1 
                qList.push(allQuestions[random])
                allQuestions.splice(random, 1)
            } 
            return qList
        }
    }
})